icould.com 2019-11-20

# Privacy policy - icould

The icould.com website is operated by Education and Employers Taskforce (we, us, our). We are registered in England and Wales under charity number 1130760 and have our registered office at Quantum House, Red Lion Court, 22-24 Fleet Street, London, EC4A 3EB.  

Education and Employers Taskforce is the data controller of personal data collected from you by this website and by related means. 

This page explains the types of personal data we may collect about you. It also explains how we store and handle that data, and keep it safe. 

### Personal data

Personal data is any information that relates to a living person who can be identified from that data. 

We respect your privacy and store your personal data securely. We do not share your personal data with anyone else (third parties). 

We hold two types of personal data: 

**Mailing list subscriber data**  
You can subscribe to our mailing list to keep up to date with our news and to receive careers information. We hold details of your name, email address and how you describe your interest in careers (exploring own career interests, teacher or careers professional, other). 

The data and consent are stored and processed by **MailChimp**. 

You can unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time.

**Career video data**  
Anyone who is featured in an icould video signs a consent form for use of their image and sound. The consent form can include name, email address, contact number and job title. We hold a paper copy of this data and may also hold a digital version on our computer system. 

### Website

**Website cookies**  

We use cookies (small pieces of data downloaded to your device when you visit a website or app) to improve your experience of our site and to track site use. 

These cookies do not identify you personally, but they use your device’s IP address to locate where you are. Some cookies may be stored on your device after you finish your browsing session. 

Visit our [ **Cookies**](https://icould.com/cookies) ** ** page for more information. 

**Links to other websites**

icould.com includes links to other (third-party) websites that we do not control. We are not responsible for these sites or their content. You should check their privacy policies for details of how they use your data. 

### Data controller

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you: 

  * By email to: [**info@educationandemployers.org**](mailto:info@educationandemployers.org)  
  * In writing to:  Education and Employers, Quantum House, 22-24 Red Lion Court, London EC4A 3EB  

We will review our privacy policy and place any updates on this webpage.  

The policy was last updated September 2019.
